https://www.icetrends.com/pages/privacy

Create Your Own
Jewelry Sets 15% Off »
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for IceRings Inc. We are committed to protecting your privacy and encourage you to periodically review this page to be informed of how we protect the information you disclose to us.
If you believe that IceRings Inc. is not abiding by our posted privacy policy, please contact us at Toll-Free 1-833-423-7464 or e-mail us at privacy@icetrends.com.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
IceRings Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on our site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. IceRings Inc. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
MY ACCOUNT
When you make your first purchase on our site, you will be asked to create an account. By creating an account, the system will remember your personal and purchase information and the checkout process on future purchases will be fast, easy and always completely secure.
Creating an account is also fast and easy: simply enter your personal information once and select your very own username and password. Then during checkout on your next purchase, just login and the system will take care of the rest. At all times, your personal information is accessible to you to review, edit, or update as necessary by clicking on the "My Account" link.
ORDER
We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and financial information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to communicate with the customer.
COOKIES
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie from our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the web site that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer.
USAGE TRACKING
IceRings Inc. database tracks the traffic throughout our site. This information is used to compile overall statistics and is not recorded at an individual level. This includes IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser type, ISP (internet service provider), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and #of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate. The statistics help us decide which products and services best serve our members and guests.
AGGREGATE INFORMATION
IceRings Inc. uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with partners third parties for purposes such as planning or executing advertising or promotions. We do not share any personally identifiable information.
SHARING
IceRings Inc. may disclose and transfer aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.
IceRings Inc. gives you access to third party partners to provide you with certain services. IceRings Inc. will provide those third parties with your transaction information and then those third parties will collect additional information if needed to provide you with the requested service, such as outside shipping companies to ship orders, and credit card processing companies to bill users for goods and services.
We reserve the right to disclose and transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the site, including personal information:
to our subsidiaries and affiliates;
to contractors, services providers, licensees and other third parties we use to support our business;
to licensors, buyers, successors or other third parties in the event of any license, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of the assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) relating to IceRings Inc.;
to fulfill the purposes for which you provide it;
for any other purposes disclosed by us when you provide the information;
with your consent.
Finally, notwithstanding any other provision of this privacy policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we believe that we are required to do so:
by law;
to comply with legal process or governmental requests;
to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes;
to protect our operations or those of any affiliated entities;
to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Icetrends.com, any affiliated entities, you or others (This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.);
to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
LINKS
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by IceRings Inc.
CATALOGUE, NEWSLETTERS, ETC.
If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalogue, newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and e-mail address to provide these communications. Because we respect our users' privacy, we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below.
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an e-mail. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though you can deactivate your account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
SURVEYS & SWEEPSTAKES
From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or sweepstakes. Participation in these surveys or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, shipping address and e-mail address), and demographic information (such as post code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
SECURITY
IceRings Inc. takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) best encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. In addition, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, send us an e-mail at  privacy@icetrends.com for more info.
SUPPLEMENTATION OF INFORMATION
In order for Icetrends.com to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources such as our affiliated websites. For example, in order for Icetrends.com to enhance our ability to tailor the site to an individual's preference, we combine information about the purchasing habits of users with similar information from our affiliated sites, and Icetrends.com. When a user makes a purchase from any of these companies, the companies collect and share that purchase information with us so we can tailor the site to our users' preferences.
SPECIAL OFFERS
Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below.
CORRECTING/UPDATING/DELETING/DEACTIVATING
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your post code, phone, e-mail or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can be done by using the unsubscribe feature in our communication.
CHOICE/OPT-OUT
Users who no longer wish to receive promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by using the unsubscribe feature in our e-mail.
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the site, without prior notice. You can determine when this privacy policy was last revised by referring to date at the top of this page. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Internet, accessible through the site. Use of the site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy then in effect. We encourage you to periodically review our privacy policy to ensure familiarity with our most current version.
